*你一定是个天使*
*You must be an angel*
*我从你眼中看得出来*
*I can see it in your eyes*
*充满惊奇与惊喜*
*Full of wonder and surprise...*
《超级青少年》
你发现拉尔夫·马奇奥了
Oh, you found Ralph Macchio.
-马奇奥  -是的  他是龙威小子
- Macchio? - Yeah, he's the Karate Kid.
他好性感  对吧
He's so hot, right?
我敢打赌他吻技也超赞
I bet he's an amazing kisser, too.
迈克吻技好吗
Is Mike a good kisser?
我不知道
I don't know.
他是我第一任男友
He's my first boyfriend.
前男友
Ex-boyfriend.
别担心  好吗
Hey, don't worry about it. Okay?
他很快就会爬回来
He'll come crawling back to you in no time,
求你原谅
begging for forgiveness.
我向你保证  他和卢卡斯这会
I guarantee you, him and Lucas are, like,
正沉浸在自怜和痛苦中呢
totally wallowing in self-pity and misery right now.
哭着说"真希望她们能和我们和好"
They're like, "Oh, I hope they take us back."
天  要是能看到他们的傻样就好了
God, what I wouldn't give to see their stupid faces.
怎么
What is it?
这真的管用吗
Is this really gonna work?
我的天  这太疯狂了
Holy shit, this is insane.
-麦克斯  -对  安静  抱歉
- Max. - Yeah, quiet. I'm sorry.
我怎么了  我做错什么了
What's wrong with me? What did I do wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
我做错什么了  我能做错什么
What did I do wrong? What could I have done wrong?
我又得重来一遍吗
Do I have to go through this again?
我看到他们了
I see them.
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
吃东西
Eating.
我就是不懂我做了什么要落得这种下场
I just don't understand what I did to deserve this.
没什么  没什么  我只有这一个看法
Nothing. Nothing. That's my whole point.
你是受害者
You are the victim here.
我知道  只是  她为什么要这样对待我
I know. It's just, why is she treating me this way?
-我不知道  -迈克
- I don't know. - Mike...
我做错什么了
What did I do wrong?
-我做错什么了  -迈克  别说了
- What did I do wrong?! - Mike, stop.
放松  放松就好
Relax. Just relax.
好吗  别再问理性的问题了
Okay? Stop asking rational questions.
我知道  我知道  你说得对
I know, I know, you're right.
-是的  -因为女人感情用事
- Yeah. - Because women act on emotion
-不讲逻辑  -一点没错
- and not logic. - Precisely.
她们完全是另一个物种
It's a totally different species.
他们说我们是"物种"
They say we are "Species."
-什么  -"感情用事  不讲逻辑"
- What? - "Emotion, not logic."
什么
What?
大伙  准备好了
Guys, it's ready.
-威尔  现在不行  -她们跟你们分手了
- Will, not right now. - They broke up with you.
-还有什么可聊的  -多了
- What else is there to talk about? - Tons.
是啊  我们在解决
Yeah, we're trying to solve
女性物种的巨大奥秘
the great mystery of the female species.
老兄  你能闻出奶酪玉米片味
Dude, you can smell the nacho cheese.
-我来感觉了  -什么
- I got that beat. - What?
-不  -不  卢卡斯  不
- Oh, no. - No, Lucas, no.
不
No!
卢卡斯  卢卡斯
Lucas! Lucas!
发生什么了
What happened?
什么
What...
什么啊  发生什么了
What? What happened?
我说过至少三英寸  三...
When I say three inches, three...
你不敲门的吗  老天
Do you knock? Jeez!
就是  老天
Yeah! Jeez!
对不起
I'm sorry.
-我以为...  -迈克不在这
- I thought that, uh-- - Mike's not here.
麦克斯想...
Max wanted to have...
在这过夜
a sleepover.
行吗
Is that... okay?
行啊
Yeah.
行行行
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
你父母知道吗
Your parents know about it?
知道
Yup.
好  那就好
Uh, yeah, it's cool.
好
Yeah.
那...非常好
That's-- That's really cool.
你来是有什么事吗
Did you need something?
没有  没有
No, no.
我这就走
Uh, I'll leave.
那你们就...你们...
I'll just let you... I'll leave you...
我的天  真不敢相信我们要玩这个
Holy shit, I can't believe we're really doing this.
比利  维勒太太  达斯汀  维勒先生  史蒂夫  南茜  克拉克老师
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Ready.
维勒先生
Mr. Wheeler.
无聊
Ugh. Boring.
是啊  无聊
Yeah, boring.
再转一次
Spin again.
违反规则吗
Against the rules?
规则我们自己定
We make our own rules.
比利
Billy.
好吧  听着  我得先提醒你
Okay, look, I should just warn you,
如果他跟一个女孩在一起
if he's with a girl
或者在做什么恶心的事情
or doing something gross,
赶紧出来  免得留下心理阴影
just get out of there right away before you're scarred for life.
-麦克斯  -我就是说说  我认真的
- Max-- - No, I'm just saying, I'm serious.
-他真的很恶心  -麦克斯
- He's really gross. - Max!
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
好吧  我闭嘴了
Okay, shutting up now.
翻译     贝七  卡卡妖  酥ki酱
翻译     MissMists  Monie
翻译     joy_bwl  李莫佟
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     大葱
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
找到他了
I found him.
他在干什么
What's he doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
他...
He's...
在地上...
on the floor...
马上就结束了
It'll be over soon.
跟某个人说话
...talking to someone.
别乱动
Just stay very still.
比利
Billy!
怎么了
What is it?
发生了什么
What happened?
怪奇物语
第三季
第三章
失踪救生员案
是的
Yes!
-你在干什么  -威尔  能把音乐关掉吗
- What are you doing? - Yeah, Will, can you turn down the music?
请以我的全名称呼我
Please address me by my full name.
-什么  -我的全名
- What? - My full name!
我的天  好吧  "智者威尔"
Oh, my God. Okay, Will the Wise,
能麻烦你把音乐关掉吗
Can you please turn down the music?
那不是音乐
That is not music.
那是...命运之声
That... is the sound of destiny!
我已经预见了未来
I have seen into the future,
今天是崭新的一天
and I've seen that today is a new day,
一个
a day...
没有女孩的一天
free of girls!
到底什么情况
What is happening right now?
威尔  别闹了
Will, come on.
一个备受库杂谭沼泽邪恶力量
A tribe of villagers are under threat from an evil force
压迫的村民部落
from the swamps of Kuzatan.
威尔  太早了
Will, it's so early.
是吗
Is it?
早吗  迈克尔
Is it early, Michael?
村民们哭喊着向你求救
Tell that to the villagers crying for your help,
孩子们是那么的害怕
the children so frightened,
他们夜不能寐
they cannot sleep.
你们真打算看着他们任人宰割吗
Are you truly going to let them perish?
还是说去拯救他们
Or are you going to come to their rescue
成为你们一直想成为的英雄
and become the heroes you were always meant to be?
至少能让我先洗个澡吗
Can I at least take a shower first?
天呐
Oh, God.
去麦克斯家过夜了  一一
霍普  你在家吗
Hopper? Are you there?
看看是谁来了
Oh! Look who it is!
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
是得谈谈
Yeah, we do.
自从高一的爱丽丝·吉尔伯特后
I haven't been stood up
就没人这样放过我鸽子
like that since Alice Gilbert in the 9th grade.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
乔伊
Joyce.
-能听见吗  -你看着
- Hello? - Just watch.
你吓到我了
Okay, you're freaking me out.
-你踩到这上面  摔了一跤  记得吗  -记得
- You slipped on this, remember? - Yeah.
它晚上掉了下来  失去了磁性
Yeah, it fell in the night. It lost its magnetism.
-是吗  -前一天我家也发生了
- Oh, did it? - And the same exact thing happened
同样的事情
at my house the day before.
然后我就在想"那真的很奇怪"
And I thought, "Okay, that's weird." Right?
为什么这些磁铁突然失去了磁性呢
Why are all these magnets suddenly losing their magnetism?
所以我去找了斯考特
So, I went and saw Scott.
斯考特
Scott.
谁是斯考特
Who's Scott?
-斯考特·克拉克  -你儿子的科学老师
- Scott Clarke. - Your child's science teacher?
他其实挺聪明的
He's pretty brilliant, actually.
然后我问他"怎么会发生这种事"
And I asked him, "How is this happening?"
他用交流变压器建立了一个磁场
And he built this magnetic field using an AC transformer
再把它插进螺线管中
and plugging it into a solenoid.
有了那根螺线管
And-- And with that solenoid,
-基本上  -慢着  慢着
- which basically  - Slow down, slow down.
我只想把事情说清楚
I just want to get this exactly right, okay?
你放我鸽子
You stand me up...
没有电话  没有道歉
...no phone call, no apology,
因为你得去斯考特·克拉克家
because you had to go to Scott Clarke's house.
是的
Yeah.
你简直太厉害了  乔伊
You've outdone yourself, Joyce.
你真行  真的太厉害了
You really have. No, you've outdone yourself.
拜托  霍普  你根本没有听我说话
Oh, come on, Hop, you're not even listening to me.
斯考特能让一些磁铁
Scott was able to demagnetize
消磁  而且他认为...
some of the magnets, and he thinks--
我不在乎斯考特怎么看
I don't care what Scott thinks!
他认为用某种机器或实验技术
He thinks that a large-scale magnetic field could be built
能建立一个大范围的磁场
using some sort of machine or-- or experimental technology.
他很聪明是吧
He's brilliant, isn't he?
他是真的很聪明  是不是也单身呢
He's really brilliant. Is he single too?
万一是他们呢
What if it's them?
造一个这样机器  你需要资源
To build a machine like this, you need resources.
需要科学家  需要资金
You need scientists, you need funding,
-数千万的钱  -乔伊
- tens of millions of dollars. - Joyce.
这不可能是巧合  霍普
It can't just be a coincidence, Hopper.
肯定是他们
It has to be them.
乔伊  不要说了
Joyce, stop.
肯定是那个实验室
It has to be the lab.
不可能
It is impossible.
-那你证明给我看  -证明
- Well, then, prove it to me. - Prove it?
-是的  带我回去  -去实验室
- Yeah, take me back there. - To the lab.
是的  我想回去看看
Yeah, I wanna go back.
因为你家冰箱上的磁铁掉了
Because some magnets fell off your fridge.
是的
Yes.
有道理
Okay, makes sense.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很有道理
It makes sense.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我现在有点忙  但我们可以在那边碰头
I'm a little busy right now, but maybe we can meet up there,
今晚  大概七点的样子
like tonight, like seven o'clock?
你懂的  当然  除非有事发生
You know, of course, unless something comes up
-你懂的  肯定会有的  -你知道的
- which, you know, it will. - You know,
发生了那么多事
after everything that's happened,
这绝对不是什么玩笑
this is no joke.
不  我没说这是玩笑
No, I don't think it's a joke.
我觉得当我约你出去的时候  你害怕了
I think that when I asked you out, I think you got scared.
我想你害怕了  所以现在你编出一些事
I think you got scared, and now, you're inventing things.
编出一些很奇怪的事
You're inventing things to get worked up about
好把我推开
so that you can push me away.
因为上帝禁止
Because God forbid
我们任何人
any of us
向前看
move on!
因为那样...
Because that...
那样就...
that would be...
那样就太过分了  是不是  乔伊
I mean, that would be too much, right, Joyce?
是吧
You know?
那样就太过分了  是不是  乔伊
That would be too much, wouldn't it, Joyce?
是不是  乔伊
Wouldn't it, Joyce?
乔伊
Joyce?
Joyce!
-你干什么  -我要借用一下
- What the hell are you doing? - I need to borrow these.
不  你不能回那里去
No, you're not going back there.
乔伊
Joyce...
乔伊  你不能回那里去
Joyce, you're not going back there...
他妈的
Son of a bitch!
要下大雨了
It's gonna start pouring soon.
我们应该去商场看个电影什么的
We should be at the mall or, like, watching a movie or something.
你不相信我
You don't believe me?
我相信你看到了一些特别奇怪的东西
I believe you saw some super weird stuff, totally,
但你说迈克之前就曾感应到你过  是吗
but you said Mike has sensed you in there before, right?
所以也许这次也一样  也许比利只是...
So maybe it was just like that. Maybe Billy just...
不知怎的感应到了你
sensed you somehow.
-但那些尖叫声  -我知道  是这样的
- But the screams. - Yeah, I know, but here's the thing.
当比利单独跟女孩在一起时
When Billy is alone with a girl,
他们会发出非常疯狂的声音
they make, like, really crazy noises.
-他们会尖叫  -是  但那是欢乐的尖叫
- They scream? - Yeah, but, like... happy screams.
-欢乐的尖叫  那是什么  -就像...
- Happy screams? What is happy screams? - It's like...
我把我妈的杂志借你看吧
I'm just gonna lend you my mom's Cosmo.
他的车不在
His car's not here.
你真想这么做吗
You really want to do this?
我有种感觉
Why do I get the feeling
我们会在这里发现各种讨厌的东西
we're gonna find all kinds of wrong in here?
《阁楼》
恶心死了
Gag me with a spoon.
麦克斯
Max?
冰  只是冰而已
Ice. It's just ice.
可能是为了练他的肌肉
Probably for his muscles or something.
他是个健身狂
He works out like a maniac.
一一  那是什么
El, what is it?
你确定要这么做吗
You sure about this?
你真像你妈妈  你知道吗
You really are your mother's son, you know that?
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
意思是...
It means...
你太爱担心了
you worry too much.
交给我吧  好吗
I got this, okay?
好
Okay.
所以我们到底在看什么
So, what exactly are we looking at here?
是那个德里斯科尔女士的事吗
Is this the Driscoll lady's stuff?
不  不  是这样的
No. No, see, that's the thing. I mean,
听我说  我本来也觉得她疯了  但是
listen, I thought she was crazy too, but--
她告诉我约翰逊总统杀了肯尼迪总统
She told me Johnson killed Kennedy.
但事实上  不只是她一个人
But, it turns out, she's not alone.
布莱克本商店  霍金斯农场  克劳利家
Blackburn's Supply, Hawkins Farming, the Crawleys,
都在过去的几天里
they've all had some supplies go missing,
出现了物资消失的情况
all in the past few days.
不只是肥料
And it's not just fertilizer.
还有农药  清洁用品  柴油
It's pesticides, cleaning supplies, diesel fuel.
这仅仅是我用了一天时间打电话问来的
And that's just from one day of calling around. I mean...
肯定还有更多
there's gotta be more.
好  等一下  让我把这个...
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Let me get this little...
把你的小故事理理顺
story of yours straight.
所以  这些毛茸茸的小老鼠发了疯
So, little rodents have gone cuckoo in their furry little minds
在霍金斯镇到处乱窜
and they're running around the town of Hawkins,
吃化工制品
dining out on chemicals.
我知道这听起来挺扯的  但是
I know how it sounds, but--
但是你有证据
But you've got proof!
伙计们  你们得承认
I mean, fellas, you gotta admit,
这可是个大新闻
it's a hell of a headline, right?
《霍金斯老鼠喜欢毒药  来自疯子的述说》
"Hawkins Rodents Prefer Poison: Nutjob Tells All."
好了各位
Guys, that's enough.
我觉得这是个...
I think this is...
大新闻
big.
一篇文章不够写
Bigger than one article.
事实上  我觉得这应该写本书
In fact, I think this has got to be a book.
《神探南茜解密
The Mysterious Case of the Missing Fertilizer,
化肥消失奇案》
a Nancy Drew mystery.
下次有人打电话来
Next time a call comes in,
做你该做的事
do what you were hired for,
把电话交给我们  好吗
and let us know, yeah?
我们决定什么是真正的报道  什么不是
We'll decide what's a story and what's not.
好的
Okay.
再见  神探南茜
Bye-bye, Nancy Drew.
不要紧的  南茜  南茜
Hey, it's okay. Nancy. Nancy!
不好意思
Excuse me.
喂
Ahoy!
我想尝一下花生酱巧克力夹心味的  谢谢
I'd like to try the peanut butter chocolate swirl, please.
不行  今天不能再尝了
No. No more samples today.
为什么
Why not?
因为你在滥用我们公司的政策
Because you're abusing our company policy.
那个男手水呢
Where's the sailor man?
抱歉  他帮不了你  他很忙
Sorry, he can't help you. He's busy.
忙什么
Busy with what?
做间谍
Spycraft.
看到什么了吗
You see anything?
我觉得我并不清楚我要找什么
Uh, I guess I don't totally know what I'm looking for.
邪恶苏联人
Evil Russians.
是  但我并不知道邪恶苏联人长什么样
Yeah, exactly. I don't know what an evil Russian looks like.
高个儿  金发  不苟言笑
Tall, blond, not smiling.
你也可以找找戴耳机的
Also, look for earpieces,
戴伪装物的  拿行李袋什么的
camo, duffel bags, that sort of thing.
行吧  行李袋
Right, okay, duffel bags.
-开玩笑吧  -怎么了
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding me. - What?
安娜·雅各比居然跟马克·莱温斯基那个蠢蛋在一起
Anna Jacobi's talking with that meathead Mark Lewinsky.
你要是不能专心  就把望远镜给我
If you're not gonna focus, just gimme the binoculars.
天啊  还有没有底线了
Aw, Jesus Christ, whatever happened to standards?
莱温斯基就是个坐冷板凳的怂货
I mean, Lewinsky never even came off the bench.
老兄  你是史上最差劲的间谍  你知道吗
Dude, you are the worst spy in history, you know that?
-住手  住手  -给我
- Stop, hey. Stop. - Give me those.
我不明白你为什么还要盯着别的女孩
I don't get why you're looking at girls.
有一个完美的女孩就摆在你眼前
You have the perfect one in front of you.
-说真的  如果你再提罗宾  -罗宾
- Seriously, if you say Robin again-- - Robin.
-别说了  住口  -罗宾  罗宾  罗宾
- No, don't. No. - Robin, Robin, Robin.
-住口  -罗宾  罗宾
- Stop, no, no, no. - Robin. Robin.
-罗宾  -住口
- Robin. - No.
- Robin. - No!
不行  伙计  她不是我的菜
No, man, she's not my type.
她甚至
She's not even...
和我喜欢的类型搭不上半点关系
in the ballpark of what my type is, all right?
你到底喜欢什么样的  一点都不酷的吗
What's your type again? Not awesome?
多谢你了
Thank you.
告诉你吧  她还在上学  而且她很奇怪
For your information, she's still in school. And she's weird.
她是个怪人  她是个鸡血女
She's a weirdo. And she's hyper.
我不喜欢她老像打了鸡血一样
I don't like that she's hyper.
她还演过戏剧  一副很搓的样子
And she did drama. That's a bad look.
她还玩乐队
And she's in band?
-不行  -现在你高中毕业了
- No. - Now that you're out of high school,
这就是说其实你已经是个成年人了
which means you're technically an adult,
你不觉得是时候进化一下
don't you think it's time you move on
你那些"追逐潮流"的老八股的观念
from primitive constructs such as popularity?
老八股观念
Oh, primitive constructs?
你就学了这些垃圾东西  在那个
That some stupid shit you learned at Camp...
什么都不懂营地
Know... Nothing?
应该是通晓天地营地
Camp Know Where, actually.
并不是  这是我从生活中领悟出来的
And no, it's shit I learned from life.
与其和那些你觉得会令你更酷的人约会
Instead of dating somebody you think's gonna make you cooler,
为什么不和你真正喜欢的人约会呢
why not date somebody you actually enjoy being around?
就像我和苏茜一样
Like me and Suzie.
苏茜
Oh, Suzie.
你是说"比菲比·凯茨更性感"的
Yeah, you mean, "Hotter than Phoebe Cates."
那个苏茜
Yeah, that Suzie.
让我们回想一下
And, uh, let's think about
你到底是怎么追到那个漂亮女朋友的
how exactly did you score that beautiful girlfriend?
没错  听了我的建议
Oh, yeah. With my advice.
因为一直以来都是如此  亨德森
Because that's how this works, Henderson.
是我给你建议  你来执行贯彻
I give you the advice, you follow through.
不是反过来的好吗  笨蛋
Not the other way around, all right, pea-brain?
维勒家
你们听到了吗
Do you guys hear that?
听起来像是雷声
It sounds like... thunder.
但是  等等  那不是雷声
But, no, wait. That's not thunder.
那是
It's...
一群巫术僵尸
a horde of juju zombies!
迈克长官  轮到你了
Sir Mike, your action.
我该怎么办
What should I do?
攻击
Attack?
好吧  我用猛击来进攻
Okay, I attack with my flail.
你没打中
Whoosh! You miss.
你打得石头铛铛作响
Your flail clanks the stone,
僵尸群正向你迫近  紧接着
the zombie horde lumbers towards you, and...
巫术缠住了你的胳膊  血肉模糊
the juju bites your arm. Flesh tears!
造成七点伤害
Seven points of damage.
不  我的胳膊
Oh, no, my arm.
卢卡斯  快看  我的胳膊啊
Lucas, look, my arm.
卢卡斯长官  僵尸群在咆哮
Sir Lucas, the zombie horde roars!
你是反击还是逃跑
Do you fight back or do you run?
不行  这是声东击西
No! It's a distraction!
这是个陷阱  不准接
A trap. Do not answer it.
什么  别接
What... No!
是一一吗
El?
不是
No.
不好意思  我没兴趣
Sorry, not interested.
是电话推销
Telemarketers.
也许我们该给她们打个电话
Maybe we should just call them.
要打给她们吗
We can do that?
-我想可以  -但是我们怎么说呢
- I think so. - Yeah, but what would we say?
什么也别说  奎萨部落仍需你们的帮助
We'll say nothing! The Khuisar tribe still needs your help.
那好吧
All right, then.
我会用我的火炬
I'll use my torch
放火把房子烧掉  牺牲自我
to set fire to the chambers, sacrificing ourselves,
消灭巫术僵尸  同时也拯救奎萨人
killing the jujus, and saving the Khuisar.
我们的英雄形象将在卡拉玛的记忆中永存
We all live on as heroes in the memories of the Kalamar.
赢了
Victory.
好  算你们狠
Okay. Fine.
你们赢了
You guys win.
-恭喜你们  -威尔  我是闹着玩的
- Congratulations. - Will, I was just messing around.
我们来好好结束吧
Hey, let's finish for real.
-接下来还要玩多久  -算了吧  迈克
- How much longer is the campaign? - Just forget it, Mike.
不  你想继续玩的  对吗
No, you want to keep playing, right?
就  就是啊
Y-yeah, totally.
结束以后我们再打给姑娘们好了
We'll just call the girls afterwards.
我说算了  迈克
I said forget it, Mike, okay?
-我要回家了  -但是
- I'm going home. - But...
-别这样  威尔  -让开
- Come on, Will. - Move!
威尔  别这样
Will, come on.
你不能走  下雨了
You can't leave. It's raining.
听着  我很抱歉
Listen, I said I was sorry, all right?
那段很棒  真的很棒
It's a cool campaign. It's really cool.
我们只是现在没心情玩
We're just not in the mood right now.
是啊  迈克  这就是问题所在
Yeah, Mike. That's the problem.
你们一直都没心情玩
You guys are never in the mood anymore.
-你毁了我们这个团体  -不是那样的
- You're ruining our party. - That's not true.
是吗  那达斯汀现在在哪呢
Really? Where's Dustin right now?
看到了吗  你不知道  而且你根本就不在乎
See? You don't know and you don't even care.
很明显他也不在乎  我不怪他
And obviously he doesn't either and I don't blame him.
你把一切都毁了  为了什么呢
You're destroying everything, and for what?
就为了能和一个蠢女孩交换口水吗
So you can swap spit with some stupid girl?
一一不蠢
El's not stupid.
你不喜欢女孩又不是我的错
It's not my fault you don't like girls.
我不是有意说这么过分的话  好吗
I'm not trying to be a jerk. Okay?
但我们都不再是小孩了
But we're not kids anymore.
你觉得会怎么样呢
I mean, what did you think, really?
我们永远不会交女朋友吗
That we were never gonna get girlfriends?
我们难道就这么整天待在地下室
We were just gonna sit in my basement all day
玩一辈子游戏吗
and play games for the rest of our lives?
没错
Yeah.
我猜我是的
I guess I did.
我是这么觉得的
I really did.
威尔
Will.
Will!
威尔  拜托
Will, come on!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
暴雨结束半小时之后才能下水
No one in the water until 30 minutes after the last strike.
别想着跟我讨价还价
And don't try and argue with me.
你们要是想被雷劈  就去爬树得了
You wanna get electrocuted, go climb a tree.
随你怎么说  我们不是来游泳的
Yeah, we don't care. We're not here to swim.
更不是来找雷劈的
Or get electrocuted.
我们找到了这个
We found this.
是这里的人掉的吗
Does that belong to anybody?
对
Oh, yeah.
是海瑟的
That's Heather's.
我会还给她
I'll get it back to her.
我们可以自己还给她
We could give it back to her.
行啊
You could.
不过她现在不在这
'Cept she's not here.
今天我轮班
Bailed on me today.
怎么了
What is this?
你们俩还想讨点奖励吗
You girls want a reward or somethin'?
不是
No.
我们就是
We're just...
助人为乐
Good Samaritans.
1985年泳季优秀救生员
海瑟
Heather.
你能找到她吗
Do you think you can find her?
不是吧
No way!
你看见什么了
What do you see?
一扇门
A door.
一扇红色的门
A red door.
救命
Help me.
救救我
Help me!
不
No!
怎么了  一一
What happened? El!
禁区  禁止非法闯入  美国政府财产
警告  禁区
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Anybody home?
我们没有恶意
We come in peace.
不要
No!
不
我们走吧
Let's go!
乔伊
Joyce.
没事吧
You okay?
没事
I'm fine.
你要在车里等我吗
You want to wait in the car?
我说了我没事
I said I'm fine.
-找到目标  -在哪
- Target acquired. - Where?
-十点钟方向  萨姆·古迪商场  -给我看看
- Ten o'clock. Sam Goody's. - Give me that.
我去
Shit.
旅行包
Duffel bag.
邪恶苏联人
Evil Russian.
慢点
Slow down.
我们要跟丢了
We're losin' him.
-你跟得太近了  -看着点路  臭小子
- You're getting too close. - Watch it, dickwad.
你好  对  我很好
Hello. Yes. I am fine.
你怎么样
How are you?
爵士健美操
大家都注意听
All right, everyone, listen up!
问你们个问题
I just have one question for you.
有谁
Who...
准备好大汗淋漓一场了
is ready to sweat?
这就对了
That's right!
现在让我们美美地开始了
Okay! Let's start it nice and easy now.
大腿都扭起来
Let's move our thighs. Yeah!
美女们  好好个热身
Yeah, ladies, warm it up.
接着扭动你的臀部
Bring it down to your hips.
开始感觉到发热了
Start feeling that burn,
全身都有感觉了  对吧
everywhere, down in the loins, right?
加油  美女们  让我看看你们做得怎么样
Come on, ladies, show me what you got.
现在慢下来  感受身体的发力
Slow now. Just isolate.
倾斜一点  做得不错
Ooh, tip that up. That feels good!
"这周很长
"The week is long.
银猫进食  当蓝在西边遇到黄
The silver cat feeds when blue meets yellow in the west.
去中国听上去不错  只要你轻轻走"
A trip to China sounds nice if you tread lightly."
"脚步轻轻"
"Tread lightly"?
-你的快递  -谢谢
- Delivery for you. - Thank you.
LYNX运输公司
-祝您生活愉快  -你也是
- Have a nice day. - Yeah, you too.
LYNX运输公司
银猫
Silver cat.
你不会相信达斯汀觉得谁是苏联人
You're not gonna believe who Dustin thought was a Russian.
-你也觉得了  -不  我才没觉得
- You did too. - No, I did not.
-你明明也觉得了  -不  我没有
- Yes, you did. - No, I did not.
"去中国听上去不错"
"A trip to China sounds nice."
去中国听上去不错
A trip to China sounds nice.
串烧热狗
去中国听上去不错
A trip to China sounds nice.
大熊猫
去中国听上去不错
A trip to China sounds nice.
"只要你轻轻走"
"If you tread lightly."
只要你轻轻
If you tread...
只要你轻
考夫曼鞋店
只要你轻轻走
If you tread lightly.
考夫曼鞋店
当  当蓝在西边遇到黄
"When-- When blue and yellow meet in the west."
当蓝在西边
When blue meets yellow...
遇到黄
in the west.
罗宾
Robin.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-我解出来了  -解出什么
- I cracked it. - Cracked what?
我解出了密码
I cracked the code.
就是它
There it is!
小心点  它可能有狂犬病
Careful! It might have rabies!
最好把它丢出去
Better get that thing outta here.
你不会想让它啃掉你耳廓的
You don't want it eatin' the tires off your car.
拜托
Come on!
这
What--
-这是什么  -证据
-What's this? -Proof.
证据
Proof?
他们不是说想要证据吗  我们就把这给他们
They said they wanted proof, right? So let's give it to 'em.
一只橡皮老鼠
A rubber rat?
不  真的老鼠
No, the real rat.
德里斯科尔的老鼠
Driscoll's rat.
你自己也说过它看起来不对劲
You said yourself it looked sick.
我们可以把它带去动物控制中心
We can take it to an animal control center,
他们能对它做点血检
they can run some blood tests on it,
-看看它怎么回事  -南希  冷静
-figure out what's wrong with it-- -Whoa, Nancy, slow down.
汤姆并没有要证据
Tom didn't ask for proof.
他让我们放下这件事
He asked us to drop the story.
那是因为他不信任我们
That's because he didn't believe us.
南茜
Nancy.
我是对的
I'm right.
那不是重点
That's not the point.
那什么是重点
Then what's the point?
你应该在和他们说话之前动动脑子
You should've thought about that before you talked to them.
他们都是混蛋  我明白
All right? They're assholes, okay? I get it.
但这报道就是很蠢
But it's just some stupid story.
愚蠢
Oh, it's stupid?
如果被解雇了就很蠢
It's stupid to get fired over.
没人会解雇我们
No one's going to fire us.
听着  如果你不想去  没关系
Look, if you don't want to go, that's fine.
只是
Just...
把钥匙给我
give me the keys.
你可真无情  你知道吗
You're relentless, you know that?
拜托
Come on.
没人在家
Nobody's home.
所有的洞都被填起来了
All the cavities have been filled.
我看着他们做的  乔伊
I watched 'em do it, Joyce.
威尔
Will!
结束了
It's over.
我觉得我快疯了
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
你没有疯
You're not losing your mind.
我也差不多
Not any more than I am.
你知道  那天我因为贝琪·佩恩的狗
You know, the other day, I almost shot Betsy Payne's dog
从栅栏后面冲过来就差点开枪  我
because it came rushing at me from behind this fence, and I...
我发誓我以为是那东西
I swear to God, I thought it was one of those things.
你知道我一直在关注着这些事吧
You know that I'm keeping a close eye on things, right?
-当然  -因为那对我来说很重要
- Yeah. - Because it's important to me.
让你感到安全对我来说很重要
It is important to me that you feel safe.
让你的家人感到安全
That you and your family feel safe.
我想让你觉得
I want you to feel
这还可以是你的家
like this can still be your home.
怎么了
What?
你觉得我发现不了吗
You didn't think I'd find out about that?
加里给我打电话
Gary called me.
他说他要把你的房子装修好挂出去卖
He said he's fixing up your house to put on the market.
孩子们知道了吗
The kids know yet?
在萨拉...
After Sarah...
我不得不离开
I had to get away.
我不得不离开那鬼地方  你明白吗
I had to get the hell out of that place, you know?
逃离那些
Outrun those, uh...
那些回忆  我想
those memories, I guess.
我是说  你觉得我为什么会回到这个鬼地方
I mean, why do you think I ended up back in this shithole?
但你有着我不曾有过的东西
But you have something that I never had.
你有了解你经历的人
You have people that know what you've been through.
你有关心你的人
You have people that care about you.
就在这里
Right here.
在霍金斯
In Hawkins.
你是说
You mean...
你是说  像斯科特·克拉克这样的
You mean, people like Scott Clarke.
那是开玩笑的
That was a joke.
那是什么
What's that?
在这里等我
Wait here.
威尔
Will!
威尔  对不起  兄弟  行了吗
Will, I'm sorry, man, all right?
我当时太混蛋了
I was being a total asshole.
拜托  你能出来我们谈谈吗
Please, can you just come outside and we'll talk?
威尔
Will!
Hey, Will!
拜托  兄弟  我们很抱歉
Come on, man! We're sorry!
威尔
Will!
它要来了
Something is coming,
它渴望鲜血
something hungry for blood.
-是什么  -会不会是魔王
- What is it? - What if it's the Demogorgon?
天呐  如果是魔王我们就完蛋了
Oh, Jesus, we're so screwed if it's the Demogorgon.
不是魔王
It's not the Demogorgon.
-威尔  你出招  -火球
- Will, your action! - Fireball!
十四
Fourteen!
直接攻击  威尔贤者的火球击中了赛索妖蛇
Direct hit! Will the Wise's fireball hits the thessalhydra!
-你会打给谁  -捉鬼敢死队
- Who you gonna call? - Ghostbusters!
-伊根  -范克曼
- Egon! - Venkman!
真傻
Stupid.
太傻了
So stupid.
真傻
Stupid.
德里斯科尔太太
Mrs. Driscoll?
她肯定没在家
Oh, she must not be home.
她80岁了  外面雨还这么大
She's an 80-year-old woman and it's pouring.
还能上哪儿去
Where else would she be?
-你干什么呢  -她可能摔倒了
- Whoa, what are you doing? - Maybe she fell.
之类的
Or something.
南茜
Nancy--
德里斯科尔太太
Mrs. Driscoll?
-真要这样吗  -德里斯科尔太太
- Seriously? - Mrs. Driscoll?
我是南茜
It's Nancy.
《霍金斯邮报》的
From The Hawkins Post.
德里斯科尔太太
Mrs. Driscoll?
注意看大熊猫和考夫曼鞋店
Look for Imperial Panda and Kaufman Shoes.
他们和吹口哨的是一起的  十点钟方向
They're with that whistling guy, ten o'clock.
-你觉得里面有什么  -枪  炸弹
- What do you think's in there? - Guns, bombs?
化学武器
Chemical weapons?
不管是什么  他们已经全副武装了
Whatever it is, they're armed to the teeth.
真好
Great.
好极了
That's great.
那里有什么
Hey, what's in there?
还是盒子
It's just more boxes.
让我看看
Let me check it out.
-不要  我还看着呢  -让我看看
- No, I'm still looking. - Lemme see it.
等一下
Hang on!
躲
Duck!
待在这
Stay here.
守着门
Watch the door.
看来我们找到你的苏联人了
Well, I think we found your Russians.
我是霍金斯警察局局长  举起手走出来
This is Hawkins Chief of Police! Come out with your hands up!
听到了吗  举起手
You hear me? Hands up!
霍普
Hopper!
Hopper! Hopper!
就是这吗
Is this it?
-这是她家  -什么
- This is her house. - What?
海瑟的家
Heather's house.
是不是很可爱
Isn't that cute, huh?
他真幽默
He's so funny.
麦克斯
Max.
我们不是故意要...闯进来的
We didn't mean to... barge in.
我们敲了门  但是...
We tried to knock, but...
可能风暴太大你们没听见
maybe you didn't hear us over the storm.
不好意思  这两个
I'm sorry, who is this
把我的客厅搞得全是水的人是谁
dripping all over my living room right now?
不好意思
I'm sorry.
珍妮特  汤姆
Janet, Tom,
这位...
this...
是我的妹妹  麦克辛
is my sister, Maxine.
你来这儿究竟是要干什么
What on earth are you doing here?
出什么事了
Is something wrong?
我们就是想确认一下一切都好
We just wanted to make sure everything was okay.
好
Okay?
-为什么不好  -她在哪儿
- Why wouldn't it be okay? - Where is she?
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你说谁
Where is who?
有点烤焦了  不好意思
Well, they're a little burnt, I'm sorry--
海瑟  这是我妹妹  麦克辛
Heather! This is my sister, Maxine.
对不起  我还不知道你的名字
And, I'm sorry, I did not quite catch your name.
一一
El.
你刚才说什么  一一
Now, what is it you were saying, El?
你们不是在找人吗
You were looking for somebody?
我  我看见
I-- I saw...
我看见你--
I saw you--
你们经理  在泳池那儿
Your manager. At the pool.
他说你们今天没去工作
He said you guys didn't come in to work today,
我们有点儿担心
so we got worried.
海瑟今天不太舒服
Heather wasn't feeling so hot today,
所以我们决定休息一天  让她养一养
so we thought we'd take the day off to nurse her back to health.
但是你现在没事了  是吧  海瑟
But you're feeling just fine right now, aren't you, Heather?
我现在好多了
I'm feeling so much better.
你俩想要块饼干吗
Do you girls want a cookie?
刚从烤箱拿出来的
They're fresh out of the oven.
威尔
Will!
发生什么了  你还好吗
What happened? Are you okay?
他回来了
He's back.
一切都好吗
Is everything all right?
都好
Yes.
一切都好
Everything's fine.
你妹妹真的不想留下一起吗
Your sister really didn't want to stay?
不  她只是...
No, she's just not...
不太喜欢热闹
you know, really a people person.
我就是感觉外面风暴这么大
Well, I just don't like the idea
让她们两个就这么离开不太好
of them out there in the storm like that.
她们不会有事儿的
Oh, they'll be fine.
我提醒过你慢点喝的  珍妮特
I told you to slow down on that wine, Janet.
好的  亲爱的
Yes, darling.
你还好吗  妈妈
Are you okay, Mommy?
嗯  我  我只是...
Yes, I'm-- I'm just...
有点儿头晕
feeling a little lightheaded is all.
都是酒的事儿
Hm. It's all that wine.
抱歉  不好意思
I'm sorry. Um, if you'll excuse me,
我得上楼去躺一会儿
I'm just gonna go upstairs and lie down for a bit.
珍妮特
Janet?
珍妮特  珍妮特
Janet? Janet?
珍妮特
Janet!
珍妮特  快叫救护车
Janet! Call 911!
快叫救护车
Call 91--
我真的很抱歉  爸爸
I'm really sorry about this, Daddy,
但是马上就会过去的  我保证
but it'll all be over soon, I promise.